Finding Aid for William C. Weber Papers 1858-1940
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Maps
  Maps are found in the outsize unbound material, as well as in the land records described above. The unbound maps relate primarily to Windsor and Essex County property, Michigan land, and to a lesser extent property in Tennessee and the West. Many published maps have been separated from the collection and cataloged individually in the Michigan Historical Collections map catalog. Some of these maps are annotated with information about Weber land holdings. The annotated maps can be found under the subject William C. Weber in the map catalog. Published maps remaining with the collection are generally duplicates of maps already in the map collection or portions that have been cut from larger maps. Most of the maps remaining with the collection are unpublished blueprints and sketch maps. Windsor and Essex County maps tend to be detailed plat maps showing urban subdivisions. Michigan maps are less detailed, but in some cases show railroads, roads, and settlements. The collection includes a number of detailed maps of the coal mining region around Careyville, Tennessee, and some less detailed maps of mining regions in the West.
  - Michigan
    - Inventories of Weber lands (Folder 3)
    - Published maps (Folder 4)
    - Survey maps (copies)
      - Alger, Delta, and Dickinson Counties (Folder 5)
      - Arenac and Iosco Counties (Folder 6)
      - Baraga County (Folder 7)
      - Gogebic County (Folder 8)
      - Houghton and Iron Counties (Folder 9)
      - Marquette County (Folder 10)
      - Ontonagon County (Folder 11)
    - Unpublished maps (Folder 12)
  - Tennessee and the West (Folder 13)
  - Windsor and Essex County, Ontario
    - Published maps (Folder 14)
    - Unpublished maps (Folder 15)